Ingredients:
 - 400gr bread flour
 - 1/4 tsp yeast
 - 1 1/2 tsp kosher salt
 - 1 1/3 cups water (room temperature)

Directions:
 1. Start with 400 grams of bread flour. Add ¼ tsp yeast and whisk until
    combined. Next add 1 ½ tsp of kosher salt (¾ tsp if you’re using table salt)
    along with 1 ⅓ cups of room temperature water. Gently mix it all together
    until a rough ball forms. No need to knead!
 2. Cover and let sit at room temperature for 12-24 hours.
 3. Liberally dust your work surface with flour and turn out your dough onto the
    flour. There is no need to knead, just grab the corners and pulling them in
    towards the center until you have a heavily floured, smooth, and taut dough.
 4. Once you have a large, round, smooth surface, start pulling the dough in
    towards the bottom, shaping it into small mound. Place it on some parchment
    paper.
 5. Flour a clean kitchen towel and place on top of the bread and let sit for
    about 1-2 hours.
 6. Preheat oven as hot as it will get with a cast iron dutch oven inside of it
    for at least an hour.
 7. Cut excess parchment paper off around the bread and score the top with a
    knife.
 8. Drop the loaf directly into the cast iron dutch oven, and before covering it,
    liberally spritz with water.
 9. Place in oven and let it bake for 15 minutes, removing the lid and then
    spritzing again with water and then baking for 15 minutes again (with no lid)
    or until completely done.
10. Let the bread cool and then slice into it. Serve and enjoy!